brint.com 2000-12-03

# Privacy Statement

Privacy Statement for   
@Brint.com: The BizTech Network

@Brint.com L.L.C. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: @brint.com: The BizTech Network.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. We provide you the the option of using browser-based cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. 

Our site's registration form allows users the option to give us contact information (like their name and email address). We use customer contact information from the registration details to send the user information about new content additions to the web site that are considered relevant by the user as well as special promotions related to learning, knowledge, networking and professional opportunities and services provided by our partners and affiliates. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

This site contains links to other sites. **@brint.com: The BizTech Network** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

We do not share any information about our users with any other party nor do we sell the lists of user information to any third parties. 

It is our policy to take reasonable measures to respect the privacy of our users. @Brint.com will take reasonable measures to not disclose the contents of your communications unless required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is reasonably necessary to: (i) comply with legal process; (ii) enforce these terms and conditions; (iii) respond to claims that any content on @brint.com web site violates the rights of third-parties; or (iv) protect the rights, property, or personal safety of @BRINT, its users and the public. 

Commercial uses of the services offered on @brint.com web site are strictly prohibited unless prior written consent from @Brint.com has been granted. Any use by you of any other user's information, personal or otherwise, for any commercial purpose or to obtain direct financial gain (e.g. mass marketing) is prohibited. Any such use shall be deemed to be a violation of these terms and conditions. @Brint.com and its services are to be used by you for your personal use only. You agree that you will not use them for chain letters, junk mail, 'spamming,' solicitations (commercial or non-commercial) or bulk communications of any kind including but not limited to distribution lists to any person who has not given specific permission to be included in such a list. 

@Brint.com has been actively contributing to the definition and implementation of the privacy standards for Internet Commerce through top executive involvement at the highest level in global standard definitions such as [The Standard for Internet Commerce](http://www.gii.com/standard/index.html) being developed collaboratively by leading global thinkers and practitioners including Internet merchants, IT vendors, consumer and community advocates, analysts, journalists and academics. @Brint.com has been serving some of the most prominent blue-chip companies that have emphasized the practice of privacy disclosures and has been enforcing the highest standards specified by these blue-chip clients. Besides serving most of the high-profile clients on a direct basis and in collaboration with the top-notch advertising agencies, @Brint.com also works with several third parties and major high-profile organizations that serve ads to this site. @Brint.com is a member of all major premier advertising networks including Adknowledge, Adauction, Flycast and Valueclick, although most of our in-house promotions are available to clients that work directly with us. We work with leading worldwide advertising agencies as well as directly with select customers. On rare occasions when we have excess inventory on hand, we channel that inventory through Flycast Network, which can provide limited run test results for the low exposure areas on @Brint.com portal. (For high exposure targeted campaigns, you can get the best ROI in terms of eyeballs by contacting us directly through our [online advertisement query interface](http://www.brint.com/query.html).) If you plan to use Flycast Network, you may like to find out more about how flycast manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site by going to <http://www.flycast.com/about_us/about-privacy.html>. 

**Public Forums** This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

 **Security** This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. For instance, users of our public discussion forums have the choice of hiding their individual e-mail addresses so that their addresses aren't easily available to programs that collect web based e-mail addresses for mass mailings. 

**Choice/Opt-Out** Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving our monthly newsletter which is the **only membership communication we send at this time to our global membership**. The monthly newsletter communicates to our global Network membership. 

**TO SUBSCRIBE:**

Please send a blank e-mail message to [subscribe@brint.com](mailto:subscribe@brint.com) and you will receive the latest issue of the monthly Network membership newsletter.

**TO UPDATE E-MAIL ADDRESS:**

Please send a blank e-mail message to [subscribe@brint.com](mailto:subscribe@brint.com) from your NEW e-mail address and you will receive the latest issue of the Network membership newsletter. You will also need to unsubscribe your OLD e-mail address by sending a blank e-mail message to [unsubscribe@brint.com](mailto:unsubscribe@brint.com) from your OLD e-mail address. You will receive a response at your old e-mail address acknowledging that its service has been suspended.

**TO UNSUBSCRIBE:**

If you do not want to receive this Newsletter and ALL  information, offers and opportunities available to @Brint.com BizTech Network Members, please send an e-mail message with the subject UNSUBSCRIBE to e-mail address [unsubscribe@brint.com](mailto:unsubscribe@brint.com). You will receive a response acknowledging that your membership has been suspended. Please note that the unsubscribed e-mail address can not be used for accessing any services of @Brint.com BizTech Network.

**Contacting the Web Site** If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact by postal mail: President @Brint.com L.L.C. P.O. Box 15635 Fort Lauderdale, FL 33318, U.S.A
